{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Rendering in React",
      "description": "React's component structure allows for quickly building a complex web application that relies on DOM manipulation. "
    },
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "Nsdlfkjsaldsad",
      "description": "Brief description of the decksdaf.kmdsakfmds",
      "id": 3
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": 2,
      "front": "How do you modify the state of a different React component?faskljlksad",
      "back": "Not at all! State is visible to the component only.adklsjklasfd",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "front": "How do you pass data 'down'kjhkjhjkhkhkj",
      "back": "As properties or props",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL's",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "sdaflkasjflkasdjf",
      "back": "Back side of card",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "fixed\n",
      "back": "Back side of cardsdafsafafs",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "New front side",
      "back": "Back side of cardfdadsafdsf",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "Front side of card",
      "back": "Back side of cardsdafdsafafs",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "Front side of card",
      "back": "Back side of card",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "Front side of card",
      "back": "Back side of cardkjhkjhjk",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 12
    }
  ]
}